(Kim Da Mi)
(Shin Ye Eun)
(Heo Nam Jun)
(Written by Yang Hee Seung and Kim Bo Ram)
(Directed by Kim Sang Ho)
(A Hundred Memories)
Yeong Rye, your boyfriend's here.
He's a friend, not my boyfriend.
Come on, have a seat over here.
You should've gone home to sleep after your shift.
Did you sleep in the on-call room again?
I was too exhausted to go home. I just crashed.
I can't even remember when my last day off was.
Your last day off was last Monday.
It's been exactly eight days, so this is your third day off.
Was it?
Gosh.
And on my precious day off, I'm stuck here doing this.
I didn't ask you to come.
Fine. I came because I wanted to.
Happy?
Look at them.
If those two aren't a couple, I'll eat my hat.
I mean, he comes all this way just for her to do his hair.
And let's be real, can men and women just be friends?
Exactly.
But she says they're not.
- Look how sweetly he looks at her. - Hey!
You two!
Instead of gossiping back there, why not wash the towels properly?
These towels reek of mildew.
Scrub them clean.
- Yes, ma'am. - Yes, ma'am.
Chirp. They just love to gossip.
Don't move.
If you move, I'll mess it up.
I know you won't.
All done.
Gosh.
I was already good-looking, but now I'm more handsome.
- Thanks. - Watch it,
or I'll shave this whole thing off.
My apologies.
Please, calm yourself, ma'am.
What time do you get off?
After I clean up, probably around 8:30pm?
Then I'll come pick you up around then.
You told your mom you'd be late, right?
Yes.
(Youngeun Market)
Sook, make a batch of fresh kimchi salad.
Gosh, it's packed in here.
Did you say you need a table later? Okay, got it.
Did you get a perm?
Yes.
Gosh. That'll last you more than a year.
- It turned out nice, right? - Yes, it did.
Why aren't you ordering the daily special?
I told you you'd be dead if you bailed on me.
- I'm not bailing. Why would I bail? - Good grief.
Food's here!
All right, you should eat first.
What?
How is it?
Give it exactly four more minutes on medium heat.
Got it. Here.
What's this?
So you switched to the one from Oepo-ri after all.
Goodness.
This one has way more savoury, you know?
Your palate is uncanny. Seriously?
Oh, my gosh. When did it get so late?
Hand me the phone.
(Menu)
(Phone Book)
(All kitchen utensils are 100 percent sterilized after use.)
Here you go.
- Gosh. Careful, it's hot. - Okay.
Enjoy your meal, folks.
Welcome in. How many in your party?
Seven.
You all can sit right here.
I'll clear this for you in a jiffy.
Just a moment.
Yes, this is Yeong Sik's Restaurant.
Ho Suk. Hurry and go pick up Su Jin.
Su Jin?
We just got a big group, so I don't think I can make it.
Actually, wait. I think I can manage.
Stop! Hey!
Hey!
Mr. Ma!
(Love and Salted Seafood for You)
What? What is it?
Why are you looking for Mr. Ma so desperately all of a sudden?
Are you busy right now?
Busy? Of course.
I have to visit a supplier and attend a merchants' meeting.
I'm swamped. What's up?
If you weren't busy,
I wanted to ask if you could pick up Su Jin.
Su Jin?
(Sunshine Kindergarten)
Su Jin. Your mom's working today, right?
Then I think your grandmother will be coming to get you.
You're here.
Hello.
Up you go!
- Have you been good? - Yes.
Did you listen to your teacher?
(Youngeun Market)
(Yeong Sik's Restaurant)
There.
Here you go.
It's rolled omelette, your favourite.
The rolled omelette is here!
Seeing how much food goes into that tiny little mouth...
It's truly a wonder.
Look at you munching away, our Su Jin?
What is it?
- What's wrong? - What?
You're not going to eat?
Su Jin, open wide.
For goodness' sake!
- Oh, my. - Goodness, I can't believe this.
- Su Jin, this makes me sad. - For crying out loud.
This little thing is already playing favourites.
She's so fussy. Honestly.
Mother, Su Jin isn't playing favourites.
She just really likes me.
- Isn't that right, my Su Jin? - Yes.
- I'm home. - Su Jin, I...
- Mom's home! - You're back?
Mom!
There. My little sweetie.
You were eating?
My goodness. Even a precious rolled omelette?
Did you say thank you to Grandmother?
Thank you, Grandmother.
- Goodness. - You're welcome, dear.
You haven't had dinner, have you?
Sit right here. I'll go get you a bowl of rice.
Make mine a heaping bowl. I didn't even get to eat lunch.
Su Jin. While Mom was at work today,
I missed you so much I thought I was going to go crazy.
My baby, my pretty little thing.
Hey!
That's enough.
With those bright red lips, all over her delicate little cheek.
Mind your own business, will you?
Whether I smother my kid's cheeks or spank her bottom,
what business is it of yours?
Come on, after the company dinner, you were completely wasted.
You were smooching her face so much...
that the next day, she broke out in a rash all over.
I was so upset that day, I swear.
Su Jin. Look, here.
Yes, here.
There. There, now.
Here.
You're so pretty.
Su Jin, whose little girl are you?
I'm Uncle's little girl.
That's right. You're so smart.
Goodness me.
I'm the one who gave birth to her, so why does he always say she's his?
Goodness.
Why didn't you and Yeong Rye leave work together?
(Juri Beauty Salon)
- Have you been waiting long? - No.
Let's go.
Hey, wait a second.
I'm getting kind of hungry.
I think I hear a babbling brook in my stomach.
"A babbling brook?"
- Let me hear. - Gosh. Hey!
I mean, Yeong Rye's internal clock is never wrong.
It always knows when it's mealtime. It's so precise.
Let's go grab a bite. My treat.
Hey, what do you mean? Were you planning on not paying?
Give me a break.
Let's go.
(Episode 7: Destiny)
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Ka Yeong - Happy birthday, dear Ka Yeong
- Blow out the candles! - Make a wish.
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Jong Hee - Happy birthday, dear Jong Hee
- Blow them out! - Wait.
- You have to make a wish! - "A wish."
Happy birthday!
- Here's your gift. - Seriously, happy birthday.
- We all pitched in. - Thank you.
Food's here!
Eat up, have some more.
Dig in.
Try the hamburger, too.
- Is it good? - Is it?
- Try some! - It's on me today.
- For real? - Yes, order more!
Let's dig in!
Excuse me, we'll take one of everything.
Order it all. Try a hamburger.
This is delicious. I feel alive again.
Thank you.
Hold on a second.
You can't just drink it like that.
Race you to the bottom?
You're on.
And when it comes to soda, I never lose.
Loser has to carry this the rest of the way. Deal?
Deal.
Go.
Done! I finished it!
Okay! I won, right? See?
Sorry about that.
(Yeonseo University Hospital)
- Give it here. - No, it's fine. I'll carry it.
I'll carry it.
Dad, would you like some water?
No, it'll just fill me up.
How about a soda, then?
A soda is just more water, isn't it?
Don't make me repeat myself.
Anyway, I'm going stir-crazy in here.
Lying in this sterile white room day in and day out.
Just discharge me.
Right now.
Dad, you're not out of the woods yet.
I've told you that already.
If you're home by yourself and there's an emergency,
what are you going to do all by yourself?
I know you're frustrated, but...
You're not me.
Have you ever been stuck in a hospital for this long?
Dad, please...
Mr. Han.
All right.
Should I take a little more off?
You have a great head shape, so we could definitely go shorter.
On second thought, I think we should stop here for now.
That way I'll have an excuse to come see you again, right?
What's there to look at? Just a sick old man.
What do you mean? I like seeing you.
Here, have some of this.
It's fresh-squeezed juice, so it's packed with vitamin C.
And it should be nice and refreshing. Here you go.
Come on.
I told you, I'm full.
It's not half bad.
- I'm home. - You're back?
Yeong Rye, you're here.
Goodness, how do you get prettier every time I see you?
You won't believe these women.
They acted like they were buying, asking about every little thing.
And then they just say they'll buy it later. Can you believe it?
After grabbing a ton of samples, of course.
The nerve of some people.
By the way, did your father have dinner?
- He finished all of his porridge. - I see.
That was Yeong Rye's magic touch again.
Really? I should have known.
That picky old man is wrapped around her finger.
You must be so tired from work. I feel so bad making you do this.
Not at all. I'm happy to do it.
Thanks for the favour.
Ever since he got sick, he's just gotten so stubborn.
He won't go to the hospital barber, and won't let volunteers cut it.
If it weren't for you,
he'd look like something the cat dragged in.
His hair...
There you go again, talking nonsense.
All right, there now.
Mr. Han.
Next time, I'll colour your hair for you.
It'll make you look at least ten years younger.
But in return, you have to keep up with your physical therapy.
You really do look so much better than the last time I was here.
All right. Now, get going.
You've got work in the morning.
Okay.
- I should get going. - Okay, dear.
- Take care now. - You too.
- I'll walk her home. - Okay.
Okay, Yeong Rye. Thanks again. Go on now.
Jae Pil.
How long are you going to leave her hanging like this?
You need to lock that down before some other guy snaps her up.
Here we go again.
Don't just let this go in one ear and out the other.
For a girl to be that pretty and also that kind.
Do you have any idea how rare that is?
You'll regret it if that ship sails. Make your move, you fool.
This kid...
It's so frustrating,
For a girl to be that pretty and also that kind.
Do you have any idea how rare that is?
You'll regret it if that ship sails. Make your move, you fool.
What?
What is it?
What are you trying to pick on now? Why do you keep glancing at me?
What is it? Tell me.
No, it's just that you look like you must be really tired.
Your eyes are all red and bloodshot.
Really? Do I look that bad?
Here, let me see.
See? Isn't that a little better?
Yes, I think it actually is.
Keep doing that on your way home.
It has a warming massage effect, so it should help.
- Okay. - Yes.
Code Blue.
- Code Blue, surgical ward, 402. - Wait, shouldn't you be going?
You're right. Don't take the bus. Take a cab.
- I got it. Go on, hurry. - Room 402.
- Code Blue. - Take a taxi. I'm going to check.
Come here for a second.
Since it just rained,
it's chillier than you think.
It's cold, so make sure you're bundled up.
All the way up.
I'm off.
Hey, you.
Hey, isn't today your day off?
Tell me about it.
I guess I'm just a work magnet, right?
Let's go.
(Yeong Sik's Restaurant)
I'm home.
My goodness. What in the world happened to you?
Tell me about it. Someone sure did a number on me.
Where are the kids?
Goodness. I sent them upstairs.
Goodness, they were just chattering away.
They're no help at all. Just making a darn racket.
I guess my life isn't exactly a walk in the park.
My family and extra mouths to feed. It's so exhausting.
You can say that all you want, but you're the one who cares most.
Mom. Your words and your heart are two completely different things.
Right. That's enough.
Have you been inside my head? How would you know?
Of course, I have. I'm the one who came out of you.
Anyway...
How's that man doing?
- You mean Jae Pil's father? - Yes.
Same as ever, I guess.
It's true what they say, isn't it? How the mighty have fallen.
Those old sayings are never wrong.
Living large and calling the shots, he probably never saw this coming.
That huge department store of his went bankrupt overnight.
And the shock of it all made him collapse.
But still, you know, she stuck by him through it all.
That woman, Man Ok, she's incredibly loyal.
Doing door-to-door sales while nursing him.
They're barely getting by now their son's an intern.
Goodness.
Mom, you could write a whole biography on Jae Pil's dad's life.
Why do you have their family history memorized down to the last detail?
It's because I've heard it a million times.
I heard it all from Man Ok herself, that's why.
"A biography?"
Goodness. That man...
Hey, sister.
Don't you think you're a bit loud for this time of night?
Fine.
How can you focus on your book when it's this noisy?
You could always go read downstairs.
I'd rather be here. It's cooler.
My room's too small and stuffy.
Sorry about that.
I'll work hard, make a lot of money,
and get you your own private room and a house with a big yard.
I'll do my best to make it happen.
I'm home.
Mom.
Gosh. Look at my little Su Jin. Were you eating ice cream?
You have some on your nose and cheeks.
It must've been really delicious?
Yes.
You're back?
You're not quite as late as usual today.
I thought you'd be even later.
And why is that?
Is there some reason I'm not supposed to come home early?
That smell.
When you grill that filefish jerky, I told you to open a window first.
Look at this. I knew it.
"Drinking at home is limited to twice a month."
Did you forget our house rules?
How can you chug soju all the time in a house where a child lives?
What kind of example are you setting for Su Jin?
And you, Ho Suk.
It was your laundry day. Did you start a load?
Then what's that mountain of laundry piled up in the basket?
Well...
And Jeong Bun.
It's been, what, two weeks since you said you would clean it?
All right, I get it, you nag! I'll do it.
Hey, I was about to do it.
But she insisted we have just one little nightcap.
Let's get our act together.
I scrubbed the whole bathroom this morning before I left.
She's really starting to take after someone we know.
I know, right? She's a total little Kwon Hae Ja.
You going to keep talking behind my back?
I ought to...
Asleep?
Yes, she's out.
Is someone using water downstairs?
Water...
Sorry about that. My bad.
She's been so fussy at bedtime lately.
Just to get her to fall asleep,
I usually tell her "Sun and Moon" a million times.
But I guess she was worn out today.
Se conked out after just one lullaby.
Mr. Ma played with her today, you know.
Who knows how many times he spun him around playing airplane.
Men are just built different, you know?
I bet...
his arms are killing him today.
Still, it's so reassuring to have Sang Cheol around.
Hey.
Why don't we ask Su Jin's mom to watch her tonight,
and we hit up Dongdaemun for a change?
- Should we? - Let's go.
Give me a discount.
Hey, ladies, come on! Just take a quick look.
Isn't this one beautiful?
Just looking. No harm in looking.
- But it's not my style. - How about this one?
Sorry, it's just not for me.
- I'll give you a discount. - No thank you.
- Twenty percent? - Sorry.
Goodness.
Unbelievable.
You think they give each other discounts?
Hey! What are you guys doing here? You didn't even call!
Goodness, girl! What's with the surprise?
Well, I'll be. Oh my goodness.
Who did you say is here?
Hey! The Three Corns!
Hae Ja!
Gosh. It's been way too long.
I don't think you've been here since you three came by last fall.
Well, these girls have been busy trying to make a living.
By the way, Yeong Rye, how's studying for night school?
I'm taking it slow and steady, but I'm set on passing this year.
Excuse me? Slow and steady, my foot!
Don't even get me started, okay?
She studies like a maniac every night.
She gets her own room to study, and we're crammed in the master bed.
The woman never sleeps, I tell you. She's nuts.
Yeong Rye has always been a go-getter, even back then.
Working all day and studying all night?
She's really burning the candle at midnight.
Hae Ja.
It's burning the midnight oil, not burning the candle.
Hey. Whatever.
- Call it a rump or call it a rear! - Call it a rump or call it a rear!
Being all together like this really takes me back.
I can say this now, but our Hae Ja was a piece of work, wasn't she?
- You're telling me. - Yes.
The mood of the room always depended on her.
But after Seo Jong Hee showed up, she calmed down a bit, didn't she?
But I wonder what Jong Hee is up to these days...
Wherever she is, I'm sure she's doing just fine.
She has to be.
Hey, I brought out drinks for you. Why aren't you having any?
- Go on, drink up. - Thanks for the drink.
Here, take the soup.
Here, Yeong Mi.
Excuse me, coming through.
Careful, it's hot.
Here you go.
All right.
Let's eat.
- Let's dig in! - Let's dig in!
Right.
Do you two have to go right to work today?
- Yes. - Yes.
Goodness.
The cabbage will be here later,
and Ho Suk and I have to make some fresh kimchi salad.
I don't think I can take Su Jin to her preschool today.
Me! I'll do it. I'll take Su Jin.
Oh, my. What's gotten into you?
You get a year older,
and suddenly our Yeong Mi is all grown up?
Of course.
I'm one of the big kids in middle school now.
Here, have some of this.
Goodness gracious.
That's a relief.
Now, we can just focus on the kimchi.
Yeong Rye!
Hey, what's all this?
"Rose Day?"
They've got a day for everything now.
Valentine's Day, White Day...
I guess this is another one of those days to confess your love?
It's all just a marketing gimmick.
When you think about it,
people are so clever coming up with this stuff.
Well, you know...
Maybe this is your chance...
to finally tell Jae Pil how you feel?
Those soap roses are actually really pretty.
(Orange rose: A shy first love)
Jae Pil? Where did that come from?
Because what's between you two is so ambiguous, isn't it?
The regulars at my shop argue about you two all the time.
Are they dating? Are they not?
Are they a couple or aren't they?
Even I can tell that you two are more than just friends.
Just be honest with me, okay?
Do you like Jae Pil, or not?
See? You like him.
We'll be late for work. Come on.
Come on.
The past is the past. You've known each other for ages.
- You could have built a fortress... - The bus is coming. Let's go.
Hey, wait up.
Seriously, why do all rich people...
build their houses on hills like this?
I mean, for them, since they're driven everywhere,
it's not a big deal.
Even when I'm rich again,
I'm definitely building my house on flat ground.
On completely flat ground.
Finally.
Gosh.
Who is it?
Yes, I'm from Judanhak.
Oh, my. Ma'am!
You've gotten some new dark spots already.
I thought they all disappeared after you used our new product.
Did they?
I was in Hawaii with my husband for a business trip.
Maybe the sun was too strong?
Oh, no. That explains it.
As it happens, my company just released a new dark spot cream.
It works like an absolute charm.
Well...
You know the actress, Jung Bo Ra, right?
She's in her fifties.
She used that cream, and her dark spots are all gone.
Is that so?
Come to think of it,
her skin has looked especially clear lately.
Right? I knew you'd noticed.
You have such a keen eye.
But it doesn't just help with dark spots...
By the way, Jae Pil's done with his medical school classes, right?
Is he an intern now?
Yes, that's right.
Time really flies, doesn't it?
Which just means we're all getting older, too.
That's why upkeep is so important.
And this dark spot cream...
What a relief, isn't it?
That Jae Pil got into medical school.
Otherwise, it would've been so draining.
The store owner's wife never worked,
and now she has to run around selling.
Goodness.
- How pitiful. - Well...
I guess that's just my fate.
If you feel so bad for me, you can buy this dark spot cream...
Honey, can you hand me my phone?
Yes, of course.
Oh, dear.
Here you go.
Hello?
Hyeon, it's Mom. Is everything okay?
- My goodness. - Really?
You're really coming back to Korea this weekend?
My gosh.
Are you kidding? Of course, I'm thrilled.
Wait, I have to get your room re-wallpapered.
And I need to get you a new bed.
Okay, I got it.
I said I got it. Mom will take care of everything.
Okay. Call me back.
So your son is coming home?
Yes.
Oh, my. I can't just be sitting here.
If I had known, I would've had the wallpaper done.
What colour should I go with?
Wait, excuse me, ma'am!
About the dark spot cream...
Dark spot...
Who do you think you are, glaring at me like that?
You'd better look away.
Why should I look away?
These pretty eyes my mom gave me?
If anyone's looking away, it's you!
Gosh.
This wench is crazy.
Hey!
What makes you so arrogant?
I heard you also ruined my crew's shake down yesterday.
"Shake down?" Don't make me laugh.
Hey.
Even if we are delinquents, let's have some class.
Shaking down kids for cash? How pathetic.
You're giving all of us delinquents a bad name, you know that?
What? You think you can run your mouth...
because you've got one?
What? Are you going to hit me?
Then you should've done it already instead of talking.
- She's lost her mind. - Hey!
- Are you going to let go? Let go! - Let go!
- Hey, let go of me! - What are you doing?
- Let go! Are you deaf? She's nuts. - Look at those reflexes.
Is she some kind of psycho?
- I said let go! Hey! - Hey, are you okay?
- Let go of me! - Is she insane?
- Yeong Bae. - Darn it.
(Koh Yeong Bae)
(Han Sae Ri)
- Hey, didn't I tell you to let go? - Hey, come here.
- I told you to let go! Hey! - Hey!
Koh Yeong Bae.
Wait up.
Hey, it's not what you think.
I was waiting for you, and they're the ones who started it.
Violence is never the answer, no matter what.
They're just a bunch of nasty wenches.
They were shaking down the weaker kids...
Language.
How am I supposed to be nice to a bunch of wenches?
You're always nagging me.
We're broke, and my dad collapsed and is now in the hospital.
With everything that's happened, can you blame me for acting out?
Hey, wait up!
Koh Yeong Bae!
So then I knelt down, and my knees just...
I'm home.
Hey, would you just listen to me?
Hey, Han Sae Ri.
Why are you here? Shouldn't you be home?
There's no one at home anyway, so what?
I'm going to do my homework next to Yeong Bae.
Hey, come on.
Hey, don't you bother Yeong Bae while he's studying!
- What? Gosh. - It's fine.
If you start chattering next to him, I swear...
- Stop it. - Gosh, this girl.
I don't know who she gets it from, being such a chatterbox.
Anyway...
Now, where was I?
- The marble bench, the makeup... - Oh, right.
Right, so anyway, I was in the middle of a massage,
She acted like she'd buy something. Don't get my hopes up like that.
Like she's the only one with a son.
She stopped her massage midway and just scurried on upstairs.
Gosh, that obnoxious woman. Always making a big deal of nothing.
She talks a big game about how she wants to help me.
- Goodness. - Okay, so...
When is Jeong Hyeon coming home?
This weekend or something, I think.
Yeong Sik told me he'd be back next year.
I guess he's coming back all of a sudden.
Still, if I were her, I'd be thrilled.
He's their only son, after all.
Wait, what?
Are you taking her side over mine right now?
Because her son is friends with Yeong Sik?
Come on.
Sides? For crying out loud, it's not like they're strangers.
Of course, there are sides. Why wouldn't there be?
After I went broke.
You know I have a victim complex, don't you?
I get upset over every little thing.
Come on, just take my side. Quick.
Just take my side, quick!
All right, fine, you're right. The rich are the worst.
Buying one little thing like that is a drop in the bucket for them.
She could have just bought it and then tended to her son.
Gosh, that darn hag.
I hope she trips and falls flat on her face!
There. Happy now?
- Goodness. - Yes, that's much better.
You're going to be the death of me.
I must have committed a terrible sin in a past life...
to be stuck dealing with you.
Gosh, I'm so sick and tired of this.
- But you know... - What?
When you think about it, it's funny how things work out.
What do you mean?
I mean, Jeong Hyeon introduced Yeong Sik to us,
and now Yeong Sik is tutoring our Jae Pil.
And thanks to him, Jae Pil got into medical school.
And you know what?
He's surprisingly a natural at being a doctor.
- Jae Pil! - Gosh.
Guys.
What's with all the drama?
Is the sky falling?
Or did a bus load of patients just show up?
No, that's not it.
It's about the Medical Students' Night this week.
Right.
Is it true that you get a huge fine if you don't have a partner?
Oh, it sounds like Chang Ui is on a power trip again.
We never had to pay a fine before, did we?
Tell me about it.
Man. I'm in huge trouble.
I'm totally broke this month. I don't have money for a fine.
Tough luck.
Right.
Come on, eat up.
- Hey, eat up. - Okay.
Hey, Han Jae Pil.
You know that friend of yours?
Who?
You know, the one who comes over to do your dad's hair.
She's just a friend, right?
Come on, set me up. She's totally my type.
If it works out, I'll treat you big time.
Beef, not pork. How about some steak?
Not happening.
It's not happening, no matter what you offer.
Why not?
You said she's not even your girlfriend.
Hey, stop just saying no and give me a reason.
Look, the answer is no.
Because I don't want to.
No, it would just make things weird.
Get a grip.
"With Rose Day just a few days away,"
"will I be brave enough to confess my feelings this time?"
"With the hope that it will, this song's for you."
This request is from Shin Jeong Hee in Hongje-dong.
Okay. Here is your song.
"Suzanne" by Kim Seung Jin.
Gosh, that's just unbelievable.
How does a sound like that come from a person's throat?
Gosh. That's hot!
Hey, be careful!
At this rate, all my hair's going to get fried.
That's why I told you to practice on a wig!
You nearly gave me a heart attack.
A wig is different from real hair.
Hey, and I bought you a snack to be my model, didn't I?
So just sit still and stop squirming.
I'm home.
- You're back? - You're here.
Do I smell something burning?
See! You completely fried my hair!
- Seriously, - It's not burned.
- I can't deal with you sometimes. - No, it's not burned.
It's not burned at all. Look.
Smell it. It's not burned.
Like Marie Antoinette, you're pretty.
It smells burned to me, though.
I'm telling you, it's not.
I'll get it.
- Just be careful not to burn it. - It's not burned, I'm serious.
Hello?
Hey, Jae Pil.
You're done for the day?
I thought you might still be there and was going to call in a bit.
Yes, I just got in.
So, what's up? Is everything okay?
Aren't you swamped right now?
I was. Totally swamped.
Because of an accident at a construction site.
I'm just now getting a chance to breathe.
Gosh. You must be exhausted.
Listen.
Are you free this Sunday?
Yes, the salon's closed on the second Sunday, you know.
Why?
Well, it's nothing major,
but there's this annual event called Medical Students' Night.
And if you don't bring a date,
they say you have to pay a fine.
So I was wondering if you might be able to go with me.
So...
A date?
Well, I mean...
I don't mind, but...
Are you sure it's okay for me to go?
All right then, I'll go.
Yes, I know that hotel.
Okay.
See you at the entrance.
Okay, sounds good.
A date? What's this about a date?
- Jae Pil asked you to be his date? - "A date?"
Hurry up and tell us!
The suspense is killing me.
- Spill it before I pass out! - Well...
He has this thing, Medical Students' Night or whatever.
He'd be fined if he went alone, so he asked me to go with him.
- Oh, my gosh. - Oh, my gosh.
This is it! It's finally happening?
You really think Jae Pil called you over a stupid fine?
This is totally a confession.
He's finally...
made up his mind. It's a confession, I'm sure of it!
Yeong Rye. Snap out of it and listen to me.
- This is your moment. - Right!
Don't let this chance slip by.
- You can't. - You get what I'm saying?
What do you mean, "my moment?" Don't make a big deal out of it.
- Oh, my gosh! - Koh Yeong Rye!
How can you expect us not to make a big deal?
- Go for it, I'm begging you! - I'm telling you, it's your chance!
You'd be a fool to miss it! You have to grab...
Stop! That's enough.
Just knock it off, will you?
I just...
We just...
think you two are so good together.
That it's frustrating to watch from the sidelines.
I know.
I know, but...
But I'll handle my own love life.
So please...
Quiet.
Of course, it's fine.
I'm only asking because it's you.
"Because it's you."
What could that mean?
Because he's comfortable with me?
Because we're that close?
Or could it be...
that he...
likes me?
Excuse me! One second, please.
- Yes? - A rose.
One rose, please.
For a gift. An orange one, please.
(Orange rose: A shy first love)
(Unforgettable memories, for new couples in love)
(Gimpo International Airport)
Hi, Driver Jeong!
How have you been?
I just got in the car a little while ago, Mother.
Okay. You must be tired, right?
Take your time, but hurry on home, okay?
Gosh. Is it because I haven't heard Korean in a while?
I'm not sure how one is supposed to "take your time, but hurry up."
I need to stop somewhere, Mother.
I know you miss me, but wait just a little longer.
Witness Jang Yeon Hee, who was to provide the alibi,
at the time of the incident,
cannot recall being with the defendant.
Therefore, based on the testimony of witness Jang Yeon Hee, alone,
is insufficient to substantiate the defendant's claim.
On the other hand, the testimony of Kim Young Soo, the sole eyewitness,
has been consistent from his first statement to his court appearance.
Taking all these circumstances into consideration,
Kim Young Soo's testimony is highly credible,
making the defendant's innocence extremely unlikely.
Consequently, the facts of the indictment...
are considered to be proven by evidence so conclusive...
that there is no room for reasonable doubt.
For the reasons aforementioned, the court now issues its verdict.
Order. The defendant is sentenced to a fine of 2,000 dollars.
(Judge)
All right, Trainee Koh Yeong Sik.
Could you explain your reasoning for finding the defendant guilty?
Per Article 307 of the Criminal Act, by the trial by evidence principle,
a finding of guilt...
requires proof beyond a reasonable doubt.
In this case, the defence's witness...
failed to properly substantiate the defendant's alibi,
whereas the victim's testimony was highly credible.
Therefore, I determined the burden of proof was met.
Good. All right.
While testimony can be an unreliable form of evidence,
in a case like this...
If a judge is left with no reasonable doubt...
and is certain of a testimony's credibility,
It can serve as crucial evidence for a verdict.
Well done, Trainee Koh Yeong Sik.
You were really fired up in there today.
You must be starving. Come on, I'll buy you lunch.
No, I still have work to do. You go ahead and eat.
Come on, let's just grab a bite.
I'm not asking you to treat me. I'm offering, but you always refuse.
- I'm starting to get offended. - Koh Yeong Sik.
Mr. Future Judge.
Hey, what?
It's me. What do you think?
Come here.
- What's with the pat-down? - Give me some space.
Gosh. This guy.
- Hello. - Seriously.
When did you get back?
You didn't say anything in your last letter.
Today.
Hey, it wouldn't be a surprise if I told you.
Can I get arrested for cussing at a future judge?
Oh, I'm so scared.
You're still as dramatic as ever.
So, are you back for good?
Yes.
I couldn't put it off any longer. My father's getting older,
and I think it's time I took over the company.
Yes, it was bound to happen anyway.
Good call.
So, why aren't you dating anyone?
Judging by the vibe back there, that sharp woman...
seemed like she might be a little into you, don't you think?
Or is there someone you have your heart set on?
What?
No, nothing like that.
I'm busy paying for my siblings' education...
and trying to ease my mom's burden.
Right. Your mother.
She's doing well, I hope?
What I missed most in the States was your mom's soybean paste stew.
Yeong Bae and Yeong Mi must be so grown up by now.
And Yeong Rye...
How's Yeong Rye doing?
(The 10th Honourable Yeonseo Medical Students' Night)
Thank you.
Bye.
I'm here.
Who are you?
Do you know me?
Hey, stop it.
I'm so embarrassed and awkward,
I want to find a hole to crawl into.
Right, so who...
Come on.
All right.
You just look like a completely different person.
So you took me by surprise.
Do I look that awkward?
Is the makeup too heavy? Should I take some off?
No, it looks fine. Why?
No. I'm taking it off. This isn't right.
I'm telling you, it's fine.
You look beautiful, really.
Gosh. I know you're just saying that.
Well then, shall we head inside, partner?
Stop.
Let's go.
(The 10th Honourable Yeonseo Medical Students' Night)
- This is amazing. - I know.
What is it?
- Are you not feeling well? - Hello.
No, I think it's just my nerves.
I'm getting a little carsick for the first time in a while.
Oh, no. what should we do?
Should I run to a pharmacy for some medicine?
No, it's not that bad.
I'll be fine in a little bit.
- Let's go. - This way.
- Jong Hee? - Yeong Rye!
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, do I know you?
I'm sorry. I thought you were someone else.
What's wrong, Yeong Rye?
What happened?
Are you okay?
(The 10th Honourable Yeonseo Medical Students' Night)
Let me see.
Let's put some ice on it before it swells.
Is that ice?
Where did you get this?
It was an emergency. What was I supposed to do?
I broke off a piece of the commemorative ice sculpture.
What? Hey!
I'm kidding.
I just asked for it at the hotel restaurant.
My gosh.
It's cold.
It's a little cold.
Gosh. I think it's already swelling up.
It must be hard for you to walk.
What on earth did you see to make you run off in a panic?
Did you see a celebrity or something?
If it's still swollen tomorrow, come to the hospital.
We'll need to get an X-ray.
Okay.
Okay, that settles it.
Come on, I'll take you home.
Hey, no, it's fine. You should hurry back inside.
I can just grab a taxi. I can get home on my own.
No, I insist. I wouldn't feel right about it.
Besides, why do we even have to do these stupid events anyway?
So I'll get on the seniors' bad side and pay a fine. Big deal.
Your hand.
Here, have some of this too.
Goodness, slow down.
You're going to get an upset stomach.
I'll get you more rice, so just take your time, okay?
There's plenty of rice.
We have a mountain of it over there.
Yes, ma'am. I've missed this taste so much.
See? I'm getting a little teary just from eating this.
Wait, I've got an idea.
Why don't you open up a restaurant in Koreatown?
I'll be your investor.
You'll be the president, and I'll be your advisor.
With flavour like this, it's a guaranteed hit. Gosh.
You've gotten even better at laying it on thick.
Is that what living in the US does to you?
Gosh.
You'd ask if I'd slathered my tongue in sesame oil.
I'm impressed by your creativity.
All right, that's enough. Now, finish your food.
- Are you ever going home? - Right.
Then and now,
I've always liked your house more than my own. I wonder why.
Why do you think? It's the food.
You're right. It's the food.
I just love your mom's cooking.
Please, eat up.
It's got a nice, hearty flavour. You'll like it.
You too, Judge Go.
Not a judge yet. I'm still a trainee.
Trainee or not.
You'll be a judge soon anyway. It's the same difference.
Of course. Ma'am, you're truly incredible.
The only reason he passed the bar is all thanks to you.
Heaven knows it, and I know it.
Hey, you know it too, don't you?
If you don't, you're not even human.
I know. Just calm down and eat.
Okay.
By the way, when is Yeong Rye getting here?
Is she getting off work late?
It's Yeong Rye's day off today. She went on a date.
"A date?"
A date with who?
(Youngeun Market)
Hey, forget it.
I can just walk slowly from here. You should head back now.
If I were going to do that, would I have gotten out with you?
Here.
What?
Come on.
What are you doing?
If you walk on that foot, it'll just swell up again. Get on.
Hey, come on, it's not that bad.
Besides, I'm heavy.
How heavy can you be? Stop arguing and get on.
You shouldn't strain yourself. I'm a doctor, remember?
Gosh. My poor legs.
Unless you want me to stand here in pain, just get on.
You...
You'd better not regret this. I'm serious...
I'm getting on, all right?
You've been warned.
Oh, I'm so scared.
- Okay. I'm getting on. - Come on.
Yes. I'm ready.
Okay, up we go.
Goodness.
Are you made of feathers or something?
You should really eat more. You hear me?
How can you be on your feet all day when you're this light?
You say that, but it sounds like you're struggling.
I am?
What? No. This is easy.
We're going to fall.
Don't!
See?
- Here we go. - Goodness.
Gosh.
- Hey. - Gosh, Ms. Koh.
Save me.
- You okay? - Yes.
Good grief.
Thanks, Han Jae Pil.
I got a ride home thanks to you, but what about you?
The seniors are really going to have it out for you now, aren't they?
Whatever. Let them.
I was a total rebel, remember?
How could I forget?
A group date in your senior year? Yes, that says it all.
Exactly. Now hurry and get inside.
And don't forget to ice it again before bed.
By the way...
You know...
Yeong Rye.
Jeong Hyeon?
Hey, Ugly. When did you get so pretty?
You getting this pretty makes me nervous.
I preferred you as Ugly. It put me at ease.
Jeong Hyeon, when did you get back to Korea?
I didn't even know you were back.
Today.
As soon as I got in, I craved your mom's soybean paste stew.
Well, Jae Pil.
Long time no see.
Gosh. You really look the part of a doctor now.
- How have you been? - Good.
It's really good to see you, too.
Sure.
- Another bottle, please. - Right away.
So I was talking to Yeong Rye's friend...
You two went to Medical Students' Night, right?
I guess you don't have a girlfriend, since you took Yeong Rye.
No.
But still...
You should've taken better care of her.
How could you let her sprain her ankle?
Hey, how is that Jae Pil's fault? She's the one who's clumsy.
Well, that's true.
But that's part of her charm, right?
She's got this subtle vulnerability, right?
Yes.
I really wanted to see her, but it was so brief.
Should I go bring her back right now?
I'll give her a piggyback ride this time. No big deal.
She can't drink right now.
It'll increase the inflammation.
It will?
Well, if the doctor says so, I can't really argue with that.
Here.
Thanks.
Enjoy.
- Can we get another bottle? - Yes.
Actually, just make it two bottles.
Coming.
Gosh. See, kid?
You really should learn to pick your battles?
Excuse me.
Now, on "For You, Sleepless Tonight,"
we have another letter from one of our regulars.
She's someone our whole radio family is rooting for, isn't she?
Let's read the letter from K in Dodam-dong.
"Today, I learned that apart from Valentine's Day or White Day,"
"there's also something called Rose Day."
"Apparently, it's a day to confess your love to someone with a rose."
"I couldn't muster up the courage on Valentine's Day in February,"
"but I think I'm going to go for it this time."
"I'm worried about what might happen if we drift apart..."
"and it gets weird."
"But I'm not going to ignore these feelings I've buried..."
"for a long time."
And she's requested Yoo Jae Ha's "My Reflection in My Heart."
I'm dying to know how it turned out for her.
If her confession went well,
she probably isn't even listening to the show right now.
Well, here's hoping it all worked out for her.
Let's listen to the song now.
"My Reflection in My Heart" by Yoo Jae Ha.
So, in the end,
my confession today...
was a bust because the timing was off.
What on earth?
What's going on with them? What in the world happened?
Whatever.
I thought I'd die hauling these two drunks on my shoulders.
Gosh, these two are a real handful.
What? Where am I?
It's so dark.
Well, ain't this a hoot?
You really have to get someone drunk to see their true colours.
Once wasted, the guy from abroad and the doctor...
are all just the same, right?
Tell me about it.
I used to think he was so cool.
Now, I see he's kind of a mess.
Goodness.
Who is it?
Mom?
- What? - Oh, my goodness.
You're heavy.
That hurts.
Gosh.
Hey, I've got a cramp!
Hey, who are you guys?
Why are you sleeping in our house?
Good question. Why are we...
Hi, kids.
Mom said to come downstairs for breakfast.
Both of you.
Hey, time for your hangover soup.
We're here.
You're here?
What are you waiting for? Sit down.
Yes, ma'am.
Is this dried pollock soup? Gosh. You're the best.
Thank you. This looks amazing.
What happened?
I don't know. I'm dying.
All right, let's eat.
- Thanks for the food! - Thanks for the food!
Good grief.
You didn't drink the booze. The booze drank you.
You feel sick and you're dying of embarrassment, aren't you?
You're so ashamed you're speechless, I bet.
You can say that again.
I hadn't had soju in a while, so it tasted a little too good.
We're sorry.
Forget it. Just eat your soup and go.
Jae Pil, don't you have to get back to the hospital?
Yes, but my schedule's a bit more relaxed today.
My hours got adjusted because of an event yesterday.
So, you're just going to hang around for a free lunch and dinner, too?
No, that's not what I meant...
Gosh. This soy-braised beef is out of this world.
It's so good. Gosh.
Yeong Rye, have some.
Here's a huge piece.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Hey, Jae Pil!
Hey, Han Jae Pil!
I heard you got wasted and passed out here yesterday.
Good morning, Ms. Park.
What a goof.
Gosh. Han Jae Pil, you're something else.
I mean, you don't even really drink. How did you end up like that?
Jeong Hyeon? I heard you had a drinking contest.
Why are you getting all competitive over something so pointless?
That's so unlike you.
Just drop it and let's go. You're really getting on my nerves.
Yes, right. I'm never going to let you live this down.
I'm getting out.
Hey. All right.
All right.
You're getting off here, right? I'll pull over on the main road.
Yes.
Hey, so...
Yesterday's medical school event, right?
But Ho Suk was making such a big deal...
about you taking Yeong Rye with you.
What? A big deal about what?
What do you think I mean?
You and Yeong Rye.
You're more than friends, but not quite a couple.
It's this weird, ambiguous thing, you know?
That's why everyone around you is making a big deal out of it.
So let's be straight about this. Tell me how you really feel.
So what is Yeong Rye...
to you?
Hey, hold on. I have a right to ask this.
You know Yeong Rye was my first love, right?
How could I possibly not know? You made such a huge deal about it.
Come on. What do you really feel?
I mean, is she just a friend?
No.
"No?" That's what I thought.
"No? Hey, you...
Did you just say "no?"
Then what's your relationship with Yeong Rye?
- Hey! Eyes on the road! - Gosh.
- You're the one driving! - All right.
Gosh, you're out of your mind.
Yes, I know.
Okay.
So what is Yeong Rye to you?
I mean, is she more than a friend?
What is she to you, man?
Hello.
What's going on today? Why's the mood so tense?
A super important VVIP is coming to the salon today.
And it's not just her. Her daughter is coming too.
The director is super on edge today.
Hey! Don't put the planter here. Move it over there.
Good morning.
Koh Yeong Rye, what are you doing? Change and get out here to help.
- Right away. - Where's Choi Jeong Bun?
It's her day off.
Fine, go.
Hey! I told you not to put that there!
Nothing beats a sweet coffee in the morning.
It's the best.
Anyway, our director is being so extra.
I mean, a VVIP is coming, so what? Why make such a big scene?
She's always been ambitious, hasn't she?
Hey, you didn't know?
She was Director Michelle,
the godmother of this industry's, protegee.
She stabbed her in the back and left to open this salon.
She even poached all her regulars.
I did hear something about that.
So, who exactly is this VVIP that's supposed to be coming today?
I'm not totally sure, but...
I heard it's the chairman of Daeyang Group...
and his only daughter.
Must be nice.
Begin.
- Welcome to Juri Beauty Salon. - Welcome to Juri Beauty Salon.
You need to bow lower. Again. Begin.
Welcome to Juri Beauty Salon.
I know you're all probably thinking why I'm being so extra, but...
Let's just say...
A VIP and a VVIP are two very different things.
And what's the difference?
They're completely different.
Their influence is what's different.
- Right. - Their influence.
Think about it. Ten VIPs can come and go,
but just one VVIP stopping by...
has a much bigger impact. You get it?
So, what does that mean we need to do today?
Do a good job.
We need to lock down that VVIP. That's my point.
- Am I making myself clear? - Yes.
I'll personally handle the chairman.
Manager Jo.
Yes.
- You'll take the daughter. - Okay.
You know the younger ones have more discerning taste, right?
The blow-dry and the brushing.
Make it gentle and thorough. Okay?
- Yes, I understand. - Good.
They're here.
Really? Everyone, get ready.
My goodness, Chairwoman. You've arrived.
Welcome.
Right this way.
Chairwoman, please watch your step.
- Welcome to Juri Beauty Salon. - Welcome to Juri Beauty Salon.
(A Hundred Memories)
Hello.
Staff stylist...
My name is Koh Yeong Rye.
Please take good care of me today.
You should have been more careful!
Sharp things scare my daughter. She's sensitive to anything pointy.
Daeyang Group's only daughter is the Seo Jong Hee we know?
I was so shocked, my jaw just about hit the floor.
Jong Hee?
Gosh. Yeong Rye.
Jae Pil.
Actually, the other day...
She has asked me to bring you.
Hello. It's a pleasure to meet you.
I will forget it.
On one condition.
You have to forget my past, too.